(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-25T02:21:29.095181",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Okay, we've reached the destination.
Right on time!
Is everyone ready?
You bet! Let's go!
All right then! Ready... set...
Jump!
Hovering high!
We're ready to greet the world!
We're voyaging forward with courage
To run toward a brand-new start
Let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea
Endlessly,
Cheerfully,
Meeting heart to heart!
Look up at the horizon together as one
A star is on the rise and it's only begun
The pivotal moment we're clamoring for
An infinite future's at our door
Yeah!
It's a timeless story with a new feel
Not just allegory, it's real
Wake up, big dreams about to come true
That means it's time to break through
Never knew we could make it so far,
but we're striving, thriving, here we are
Achieving the impossible,
we're virtually unstoppable
We can't sit still, we just keep moving
Now everybody sing!
We're making our way to the next dimension
We'll reinvent the world that we live in
We'll greet every day with new intentions
Break conventions, run right through!
This is it!
Been smashing barriers left and right
That's our myth!
Strong as we ever were, scaling heights
It's endless!
So get together, let's reunite!
Reach up, reach out, the future's bright
We're ready to seize the day
Traversing the pathways
Discovering highways to everywhere
Step by step
Gathering stories that we can share!
Get ready to lead the way
With each generation, a shining sensation
A dream unfurls
Let's make friends
Making a moment of history
Joyfully
Follow me
We'll connect the world!
They'll hear our song ringing out over hills and oceans
Our legend grows and continues!
We'll carry on starting now, setting hearts in motion
Connecting all of the world!
We're making our way to the next dimension
We're living out the dreams we believe in
Excitement beyond our comprehension
There's no question we'll break through! (Don't relent!)
We'll keep aspiring to excel (That's our myth!)
It's awe-inspiring, going well! (Represent!)
So light the fire and let's rebel!
The future's brighter, we can tell!
We're ready to
We're ready to change the world!
Yay!
Myth Medley! Myth Medley! Myth Medley! Myth Medley!
What are you doing? - I'm...
Oh, you too! Both of you guys are extra little strange right now.
We're doing crazy faces!
Why are you being so silly? Come on, we got a show to do!
We got a show to do!
Ina, come on! Come on! Ganbare!
I know the floor is nice, but... - It is really nice. It's smooth.
All right, minna-san, thank you for coming to the show today to celebrate Myth's... you guessed it, 5th Anniversary!
Yay!
How was the medley? A nice throwback! We've made so many songs together.
Yeah, nostalgic!
Putting it all together like that is like, really emotional.
And it's not just like our 5th anniversary, it's also Hololive English as a whole! 5 years!
Yay!
We're all 5!
You know, we've also achieved so much in the last 5 years, you know?
We've had 3 EN concerts... My voice cracked a bit, sorry...
And we had a lot of friends join us over the years, and...
You know, in the end, I'm just really happy to be performing with you guys.
So much fun.
Yeah! But we can't get too emotional just yet though, because we have a show to do!
Uh-huh, uh-huh, yes! Anyways, anyways, anyways!
There's a hashtag right here, right here. - Yes, yes.
Over here! Take lots of pictures, screenshots, and post them on social media #Myth5Years!
Make us trend!
Trending, get it trending! Number one!
If you want, you don't have to if you don't want to.
Just kidding! If you don't do it, we'll be sad. We'll be angry! We'll get you!
Okay. Besides that, everybody, this is important.
I'm just checking, making sure you guys are all here legally.
Tada!
Woah! Did you guys all receive a ticket?
Oh, I remember that!
It's me! It's me, that's me! - Oh, we look so cool!
Yeah, I think I gave you mine at the bar. It was kind of spicy, remember?
Oh! Spicy!
I accosted you on the street, yeah, if you remember.
Ah, right! Oh, that's what you were up to.
I, uh... I might have trespassed...
What? Oya, oya? What did you do? Ina, would do such a thing? What did you do?
Don't worry, it's fine. It's fine, it's fine.
You know, my Ninomae... Ninomae Ina'nis...
What? Sorry. What did you do? You don't want to share?
Nothing! I did nothing illegal.
Fine, don't tell me, keep your secrets. - Fine, we're used to it. It's been 5 years.
Now that we know that everybody's here with their tickets and allowed to be here, we'll be singing a lot on this stage today in different combinations and different fun songs and so on.
But speaking of the stage... - Oh, yeah! Look at the stage!
That smooth floor. - Beautiful stage! Gorgeous!
So stylish, fancy! Look at that chair, look at that couch! How much is that couch? Can I lie on it?
Get your priorities straight! - Look at that chandelier, can I swing on it? - Oh my god!
I really like that one.
Are you stealing that?
Is that a heart? What's the heart for?
It's suspense.
Did it just change color? I think it just gained some color.
Could it be that it's reacting to everybody's reactions in the chat?
And their feelings? It's changing color according to that?
Are you guys getting excited?
Chat, you guys have an important job to do now, right?
They're always doing something. It must be that...
It's their power and their energy! It's flowing for us!
Well, I look forward to seeing how it develops from here out.
So you know what you're gonna do, right? You're gonna get out your keyboards and you're gonna type some things.
Hackerman, yeah!
Give us your energy! Give it to us!
Yeah, not like we're trying to shake you down or anything. - I feel like I'll take them down right now.
Okay, all right. We're choosing violence again today.
Why are you so violent? - We should be wholesome!
Five years later, she's done. - I'm just really happy to be here.
Oh no, they know the real me now. Sorry, I'm sorry.
I feel like I'm always the one that makes mistakes. - It's all the eagerness. I apologize.
There's not a lot of time for yapping too much today, it would seem.
We're gonna dance our hearts out, sing our hearts out for you guys.
And man, we've been doing a lot of that these days. I think Hololive Myth deserves a trophy.
A little reward! A treat, perhaps? Cookies? Cookies!
Cookies sound good, too. Maybe a cookie-shaped...
...or a trophy made out of a cookie.
Or a trophy-shaped cookie! You hear that, management?
You better be having some reward for us!
That's so demanding. Well, that's fine. That's okay.
In that case, I know how we can kick this off.
Maybe it's a little cheesy, but I thought the three of us could jump in the air and go "Whee!"
Like "3, 2, 1, jump!" And then the camera goes "Whee!" and we fly into the air and go to the next song.
I get it, I get it. I get you.
Done it before. Okay, then let me do it!
No punching, no violent thoughts, Ina! Don't touch the camera, I know what you're thinking!
Just one uppercut? - Not one! Zero!
Okay, let me do it, okay? Here we go.
Ready? Next song start!
3, 2, 1, jump!
ビビデバ
[Title: Bibideba]
つまらないデイズ もう散々ね！ 奇跡願っているだけの人生
Dull days are so done! Just living a life wishing for miracles...
WATCH ME DO DO DO DO DO 呪術秘中 トリック無しのマジック
WATCH ME DO-DO-DO-DO-DO... Secret spell, magic with no tricks!
WANNA BE FREE! だってまだふりだし (THE PARTY AIN'STARTED)
WANNA BE FREE! After all, we're still at square one (THE PARTY AIN'T STARTED)
HEY タクシー ちょっと宇宙まで
HEY TAXI, take me to outer space!
秒針は音を立てて 夜を急かす魔物のよう
The second hand ticks loudly, like a monster hurrying the night along...
人生は一瞬にして 溶ける魔法
Life is magic that melts away in an instant...
それならば駆け抜けて想い通り！
In that case, dash through just as you please!
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗って DRIVIN' あたしは大変身メイクアップ！
Hop into a stylish carriage, DRIVIN'... I'm having a big makeover, MAKE UP!
我儘のまにまに煌めきに注意
Doing as I selfishly please, beware of my sparkle!
洒落た街で DANCIN' 左様ならグッバイ劣等感
DANCIN' in a stylish city! Farewell, goodbye, complex of inferiority!
何時かは喝采 クラップ・オウ・デエンス 皆々御唱和あれ！
One day, cheers and applause, CLAP O' DANCE! Everyone, chant along!
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA YEAH
混散がっても仕方が無い ガラスシューズで踊る TONIGHT
Can't help it even if things get confusing, dancing in glass shoes TONIGHT!
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA YEAH
今夜に明日など無い ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう？
There's no tomorrow tonight, so whoever dances freely wins, right?
DANCE! ラリラリホ どんな問題も解は一つ
DANCE! Lari-Lari-Ho! No matter the problem, there's only one answer.
白紙も正解も間違いも愛す 本物のあたしの理想
Loving blank slates, correct answers, and mistakes—the real me's ideal!
なんだか世界は限界の気配がして
Somehow the world feels like it's reaching its limits...
ただただ安心じゃ心配 今すぐ JUMPIN', JUMPIN' OUT
Being completely safe makes me anxious, right now JUMPIN', JUMPIN' OUT!
CHITTY-CHITTY BANG-BANG 唯々諾々に聞き換んイダクタフ日々に
CHITTY-CHITTY BANG-BANG, obediently accepting those dull daily routines...
ギリギリ爆発気味 たった今発散してしまおうか
On the verge of exploding, shall we blow off some steam right now?
まだまだビィビィ段巧みに乱写
Still not enough, firing wildly with precision...
一発じゃあ打ち足りないわ ついに導き出した君にアンサー
One shot isn't enough, bringing forth an answer to you at last!
灰になるまで踊っていよう
Let's keep dancing until we turn to ash!
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA YEAH
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗って DRIVIN' あたしは大変身メイクアップ！
Hop into a stylish carriage, DRIVIN'... I'm having a big makeover, MAKE UP!
我儘のまにまに煌めきに注意
Doing as I selfishly please, beware of my sparkle!
洒落た街で DANCIN' 左様ならグッバイ劣等感
DANCIN' in a stylish city! Farewell, goodbye, complex of inferiority!
何時かは喝采 クラップ・オウ・デエンス 皆々御唱和あれ！
One day, cheers and applause, CLAP O' DANCE! Everyone, chant along!
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA YEAH
こんがらかったって仕方が無い ガラスシューズで踊る TONIGHT
Can't help it even if things get messy, dancing in glass shoes TONIGHT!
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA YEAH
今夜に明日など無い ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう？
There's no tomorrow tonight, so whoever dances freely wins, right?
Alright, let's get it started!
耽溺で結構
It's fine to indulge
Easy peasy pow
頭の中でこねくり回す
Kneading thoughts inside my head
のちのペルソナに繋がる
Linking to the persona that comes later
生まれたてのアイデアと
A newly born idea,
多少ムラがあるが疑うこともなく
Inconsistent as it may be, without a doubt,
才ある者が群がる
talented ones gather around.
What about you? ただ探求
What about you? Just pursuing,
妄想膨らます
expanding my delusions.
居ても立っても居られない分かつ
Unable to sit still, splitting pathways,
岐路の先に待つ結末は
the outcome waiting beyond the fork ahead:
麒麟児 大器晩成
A prodigy, a late bloomer,
はたまた臥竜鳳雛の末端
or the lowest of hidden geniuses.
選ぶのは自分 血気盛んに決起
You decide—rising up full of vigor.
名と共に残す生きた証
Leaving behind proof of life alongside my name,
例えばここで言い切った歌詞
like these lyrics declared right here.
興味本位が充満
Filled with pure curiosity,
光陰矢の如しあっという間
time flies like an arrow in a flash.
Living with no hesitation
時間を忘れて耽る on, and on, and no joke
losing track of time and indulging, on and on...
Kicking back, coming up next level
The future's only colored by the cleverest of rebels
飽和した時代を過去にすべく
To leave this saturated era in the past,
狂気孕んだ種が芽出す
a seed pregnant with madness sprouts,
いずれ実り昇華
eventually bearing fruit and sublimating.
乱れ咲いた桜花浴びる
Basking in wild-blooming cherry blossoms,
ホープ, turn it up
hope, turn it up!
熱狂! Just a little madness, you can't take...
Nekkyo! Just a little madness, you can't take...
熱狂! Can't hide, it's a new generation creation
Nekkyo! Can't hide, it's a new generation creation
熱狂! Tearing up the canvas, won't be what...
Nekkyo! Tearing up the canvas, won't be what...
熱狂! Can't fight this uprising outbreak...
Nekkyo! Can't fight this uprising outbreak...
Too wild, too loud
Unbound and unrefined
Find out that cloud of noise, it's only in...
Find out that cloud of noise, it's only in our...
Right now, it's time
No doubt we're moving on
I'm drawing my ideal world outside their lines
思い立ったその瞬間から
From the very moment the idea struck,
気付けば今やもう習慣
before I knew it, it became second nature.
Wrecking all expectations
初心を忘れず耽る on, and on, and no joke
never forgetting my roots and indulging, on and on...
愛する真似し
Pretending to love,
罪深き真似し
pretending to be sinful,
猛った衝動 情熱は依然止まらない
a raging impulse and passion still won't stop.
Never hitting the brakes to prove I got...
And manifest a world you'll never discern...
And manifest a world you'll never discern as real...
Shout it out!
熱狂! Just a little madness, you can't take...
Nekkyo! Just a little madness, you can't take...
熱狂! Can't hide, it's a new generation creation
Nekkyo! Can't hide, it's a new generation creation
熱狂! Tearing up the canvas, won't be what...
Nekkyo! Tearing up the canvas, won't be what...
熱狂! Can't fight this uprising outbreak...
Nekkyo! Can't fight this uprising outbreak...
人様に誇れずとも
Even if it's nothing to brag about to others,
自分の背中押せるような夢があればそれでいい
if I have a dream that pushes me forward, that's fine.
たられば終わるよりも只管にもがく
Rather than ending in 'what ifs', I'll struggle endlessly.
止まない雨はないと信じ 今に様変わる
Believing no rain lasts forever, things will change soon.
Words like "gifted", "prolific", you better...
Words like "gifted", "prolific", you better be specific
Broad strokes, blowing smoke, blink and you...
Broad strokes, blowing smoke, blink and you could miss it
These words illicit visions of a future so...
These words illicit visions of a future so exquisite
A masterpiece you've never seen, awaiting...
A masterpiece you've never seen, awaiting the few...
知らないことがあれば研究
If there's something I don't know, I research it.
出来ないことがあれば練習
If there's something I can't do, I practice it.
姿勢は前めり故の熱中
An eager stance leads to total devotion.
成功の真反対にある
Failure, which lies opposite of success,
失敗が一番の近道だ
is actually the shortest shortcut.
You can do it さあ行こう 時は満ちた
You can do it! Come on, let's go, the time has come!
It's about time
Stars aligning, I'll design it all, I'm...
Stars aligning, I'll design it all, I'm already on my way
滾る音が歪み昂る体中満ちるまで
Surging sounds distort until my body overflows...
And if it's lost, I'll find it, all this...
And if it's lost, I'll find it, all this blind resolve...
Vicious, and vivid, and striking, my
熱狂!
Nekkyo!
Vicious, and vivid, and striking, my 熱狂!
Vicious, and vivid, and striking, my Nekkyo!
誤解すんなよ こんな滑稽な
Don't misunderstand, it's laughable
サッと過ぎ去る毎日 (エブリデイ)
How time flashes by every day
Another prisoner of fate no one could fake out
Stay awake now, you know you wanna fire away
Now there's no question where the fault lies
These days I struggle just to empathize
もう戻らないって分かっているんだろう
There's no going back, and you know that
Cast a blessing on my cursed role
And feed this bleeding egotistical soul
Before you know it, it's the moment you've lost all control
遠き日の夢を見るたび
Every time I dream of days gone by
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I wonder why I came to be
嗚呼 美しい春の日々だな
Ah, such beautiful, youthful days
この目に焼き付けておこうかな
I should burn their images into my mind
もう少し強くならないとな
But I'd have to be a little stronger first
身分不相応の嫉妬に塗れた
Dripping in jealousy that's a bit too daring
ちょっと足りないエクスタシー
An ecstasy that's just a little bit lacking
誤解も解けないまま私 人を傷つけて
I hurt somebody without ever opening my eyes
一粒の才すら無いわ
But there's no talent here, it's clear to see
転がり落ちたジゴロサイ
The rigged dice falls and rolls
貴方の愛に気付けないまま
Before I ever notice your love and affection
Cast a blessing on my cursed heart
Why keep me breathing while it's falling apart?
どうか神様教えてくれますか
Pray tell me, God
どうか神様 教えでくれますか
言葉少なに貴方に捧ぐ
I give to you silently
今にも消えてしまいそうなこの命を
My life that's about to burn out
嗚呼 愛おしいセピア色した
Ah, and these sepia-toned sights
何より大事なこの景色を
they're most precious of all
もう少し見ていたいような
I wish I could see them a bit more...
I'm always gonna be my own worst enemy
Everything I ever wanted was in front of me
The angels on my shoulder still cannot agree
If I was somebody else, could I get everything?
I'm always gonna be my own worst enemy
Everything I ever wanted was in front of me
The devils on my shoulder never let me be
Obsessing over tomorrows that I'll never see
Somebody save me
My world is caving in cuz I thought I deserved it all for free
遠き日の夢を見るたび
Every time I dream of days gone by
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I wonder why I came to be
嗚呼 美しい蒼い日々だな
Ah, such beautiful, youthful days
この目に焼き付けておこうかな
I should burn their images into my mind
もう少し強くなならないとな
But I'd have to be a little stronger first
はらり はられ 今踊り踊れ
Fluttering, fluttering, dance now, dance
恋焦がれ遊べさぁ
Play in the longing of love
喰らって唄え 花に紛れ
Devour and sing, lost among the flowers
今を取り戻せ
Reclaim the present
酔狂に遊べさぁ
Play with abandon
ここで踊れ
Dance here
一二三四伍 あっちゅーま時間が過ぎてく
One, two, three, four, five, in no time, time passes
寄り取り見取りさ 祭り囃子
A choice of festival music
あれもこれも籠放り込み
Throw everything into the basket
欲にまみれて生きていたい
I want to live covered in desire
人生寄り道回り道
Life, detours, roundabout ways
生きたいように生きなはれや
Live as you wish
はらり はられ 今踊り踊れ
Fluttering, fluttering, dance now, dance
恋焦がれ遊べさぁ
Play in the longing of love
喰らって唄え 花に紛れ
Devour and sing, lost among the flowers
今を取り戻せ
Reclaim the present
酔狂に遊べさぁ
Play with abandon
ここで踊れ
Dance here
ひゅるひゅるりーらら ひゅるりらぱっぱ
Hyu-ru hyu-ru ri-ra-ra, hyu-ru ri-ra pa-pa
ひゅるひゅるりーらら ひゅるりらっぱー
ひゅるひゅるりーらら ひゅるりらぱっぱ
Hyu-ru hyu-ru ri-ra-ra, hyu-ru ri-ra pa-pa
ひゅるひゅるりーらら ひゅるりらっぱー
ちるぬを あっちゅーま時間は過ぎ
Dust and ashes, in no time, time passes
さぁ酸いも甘いも祭り囃子
Taste both the sour and the sweet of the festival music
味わい尽くしてしまいましょう
Let's savor it all
さぁ何かから平らげよう
What shall we devour first?
人生気付けば矢のごとし
Life, if you notice, is like an arrow
命の花を打ち上げましょう
Let's launch the flower of life
はらり はられ 今踊り踊れ
Fluttering, fluttering, dance now, dance
恋焦がれ遊べさぁ
Play in the longing of love
喰らって唄え 花に紛れ
Devour and sing, lost among the flowers
今を取り戻せ
Reclaim the present
酔狂に遊べさぁ
Play with abandon
ここで踊れ
Dance here
ひゅるひゅるりーらら ひゅるりらぱっぱ
Hyu-ru hyu-ru ri-ra-ra, hyu-ru ri-ra pa-pa
ひゅるひゅるりーらら ひゅるりらっぱー
ひゅるひゅるりーらら ひゅるりらぱっぱ
Hyu-ru hyu-ru ri-ra-ra, hyu-ru ri-ra pa-pa
ひゅるひゅるりーらら ひゅるりらっぱー
花よ花よ誇りなさい
Oh flower, oh flower, be proud
まごうことなく君のまま
Unmistakably remain as you are
上を向いて御覧なさい
Look up and see
最後の日まで花であれ
Be a flower until the last day
はらり はられ 今踊り踊れ
Fluttering, fluttering, dance now, dance
恋焦がれ遊べさぁ
Play in the longing of love
喰らって唄え 花に紛れ
Devour and sing, lost among the flowers
今を取り戻せ
Reclaim the present
酔狂に遊べさぁ
Play with abandon
ここで踊れ
Dance here
はらり はられ 今踊り踊れ
Fluttering, fluttering, dance now, dance
誰かれも遊べさぁ
Play with everyone
喰らって唄え 離れ離れ
Devour and sing, separated, separated
でも花火上げて
But light fireworks
酔狂に遊べさぁ
Play with abandon
ここで踊れ
Dance here
ひゅるひゅるりーらら ひゅるりらぱっぱ
Hyu-ru hyu-ru ri-ra-ra, hyu-ru ri-ra pa-pa
ひゅるひゅるりーらら ひゅるりらっぱー
ひゅるひゅるりーらら ひゅるりらぱっぱ
Hyu-ru hyu-ru ri-ra-ra, hyu-ru ri-ra pa-pa
ひゅるひゅるりーらら ひゅるりらっぱー
ああしたい？ こうしたい？ どうしたい？
Do you want to do this? Do you want to do that? What do you want to do?
まるで死んでるみたい
It's almost like I'm dead.
石の上にも三年？
Three years on a stone too?
でもそんなんじゃ AI サーキュレーション
But at that rate, it's just AI circulation.
今日やっと始まるストーリー
A story that finally begins today.
生まれたての卵のような イン・モーション
Like a freshly laid egg in motion.
カラカラ飛び出し いい気みだななんて
Popping right out of its shell, saying "serves you right",
君は決め顔で (せーのっ！)
you say with a serious face, "Ready, go!"
永遠を願った夢に
To the dream that wished for eternity,
終わりを告げる朝が来て
comes the morning announcing its end.
お砂糖でできたその涙
Those tears made of sugar...
煮つめ 煮つめ 見つけた心
Boiled down, boiled down, I found a heart.
甘くほろ苦い キャラメルのように
Bittersweet, just like caramel,
からまるリボンは 呪いの鎧だけど
the entangling ribbon is a cursed armor, but...
この気持ちはそう この気持ちにしか
these feelings, yes, only to these feelings,
きっとわかんないから
will surely be understood.
君と手と手繋いで
Holding hands with you,
ひとつひとつ叶えていこう
let's make them come true one by one.
僕らの物語は
Our story
今日へ続く約束
is a promise that continues to today.
色とりどりの 真っ黒な歴史
A colorful, pitch-black history,
愛おしい私の歴史
my beloved history.
誰も知らない 真っ白なページ
A blank page nobody knows,
更新していく
I'll keep updating it.
話したくない綻びは
Flaws I don't want to talk about,
話したくない喜びで
with joys I don't want to share,
継ぎ接ぎだらけのこの心
this heart full of patches,
継ぎ 紡ぎ 繋いだところ
stitched, spun, and bound together.
あこがれ 恋いこがれ マジあこがれ
Longing, yearning, super longing!
全部 全部 全部 全部
All of it, all of it, all of it!
プリンみたいにひっくり返して
Flip it over like a pudding!
キャラメル キャラメル マイ・オー・フレーバー
Caramel, caramel, my own flavor!
どこ居たい？ ここ居たい？ 消えないで
Where do you want to be? Stay here? Don't disappear!
朝のままじゃ ぼくはパズルのピース
If it stays morning, I'm just a puzzle piece.
でもそんなんじゃ嫌だ！
But I don't want that!
僕ら決め顔で せーの！
With a serious face, ready, go!
好きの切り札は 自分自身で選ぶの
I choose the trump card of love myself,
運命の赤い リボンを手繰り寄せて
reeling in the red ribbon of fate.
この気持ちはそう この気持ちにしか
These feelings, yes, only to these feelings,
きっとわかんないから
will surely be understood.
君と手と手繋いで
Holding hands with you,
ひとつひとつ叶えていこう
let's make them come true one by one.
僕らの物語は
Our story
今日へ続く約束
is a promise that continues to today.
君と手と手繋いで
Holding hands with you,
ひとつひとつ叶えていこう
let's make them come true one by one.
僕らの物語は
Our story
今日も続く約束
is a promise that continues today.
色とりどりに 真っ黒な歴史
A colorful, pitch-black history,
愛おしい僕らの歴史
our beloved history.
残さず食べて 全部糧にして
Eat it all up, turn it into nourishment,
更新していく
and keep updating.
Yay!
What are we doing?
Welcome back, Calli!
Oh, hi. Hey.
You guys look a little tired.
I thought we were posing for the Myth album cover that's not coming out, by the way.
Misunderstanding, misunderstanding!
Why? We have a mixtape, what?
Someday, someday.
Did you guys enjoy the songs so far?
What did you think?
We did a really cute one, Ina!
Yeah! Caramel ribbon cursetard!
Yeah! Your voices fit really, really well with that song.
Oh, thank you!
Yeah, it's a really good song.
Yeah, me and Ina were like, "What song should we do together?"
And I was like, "Ah, I wonder if Ina would let me do a Monogatari song?"
I was like, "Monogatari please!" And she's like, "Yeah!"
Excuse me, you're talking to Ninomae Ina'nis, you know!
Of course I'm gonna say yeah!
But we all like Monogatari, right?
We do, yeah.
Calli could've done it too, huh?
Sure, yeah, I would've.
We could've had her doing the...
Now I wanna see that!
I can do it now! I can do it now!
Ah, straight up, that's creepy!
I can do it more cute.
I'll do as cute as I can!
How about everybody's solos, though?
Yeah!
Oh yeah, except mine!
Mine next!
There's no Calli solo!
You guys know I could rap that fast?
Like, I was super surprised!
Kind of crazy.
Impressive.
Yeah, well, well, well.
かっこいい Calli!
Cool Calli!
I did my best! It was like enough...
Enough like, "Oh yeah, she did it."
Plus the dancing was pretty cool, so.
Oh yeah!
Good job!
And Ina too! Very impressive!
Oh goodness, that's a really challenging song.
Her dancing has leveled up so much!
Yeah.
Cute, beautiful!
Demure.
Yeah!
It was a lot of fun. It was difficult, of course. My heart rate shot through the roof, but...
We did it! We killed it!
Yeah! And then me and Ina did some air guitar.
We had... Oh!
My original song, Sepia... Very close song to my heart.
And neat-o guitar, by the way.
Yeah, yeah, I loved the purple guitar.
Yeah, so cool.
What's still missing now?
Well, there are a couple songs missing, aren't there?
Wawa's song, right? Combination.
A lot of combinations.
And mine and Calli's combination song! Wonder what you guys are gonna see!
I wonder... I wonder, I wonder.
I want to say that the song for me and Calli was also chosen, kind of, suggested by me. Thank you, Calli!
Thank you for being okay with it!
It's a nice song. Oh my gosh, yeah, I don't want to spoil anything, but it's pretty good!
Yes!
And my solo will be epic and hype, so...
Why'd you choose it? Can you give a hint? Can you give a hint? I know it's about to happen pretty soon here, but...
No, damn it! Okay!
All right, all right.
Why? I'm a toddler, why?
But yes, we still have a lot of our show left over, so...
...don't tune out. There's lots more. Can't wait to...
Stay right there! Don't move!
Wait, and continue to watch until the end!
And use the hashtag, don't forget that.
Okay, hashtag.
Are you ready to move on? Move on!
Okay, what should we do?
I don't know, let's just play with the camera.
What do you want to do, Ina? What do you want to do the most?
I know, actually... Oh...
What are you gonna do?
Not something violent, right?
Not something v...
Okay.
She's gonna do something violent! She's gonna do something violent! Oh!
Yay!
Hey!
Dear God, I've come to repent my sins.
Let Your blood wash me clean, for I'm...
...I'm...
...I'm... I'm a rotten girl...
I swore I'd never sin again
But my patience's running thin
The temptation flowing through my veins
I'm bounded by these shackles of shame
I promised I'd indulge no more
But my heart I can't ignore
In my dreams, they're turning up the heat
I'm a dirty, rotten girl
On lock, underneath the bleachers
Just watch! Look beyond the smoke and mirrors
Heartstruck?! Shun the nonbeliever!
Our operation would never be complete
Red-hot tension with each whisper
Snapshot! Quiet moans and muffled whimpers
Come on, can't you feel the fever
Rising up? Rising up to the sky?
As testaments echo, fear ignites beneath my skin
The Lord sayeth, "Halt thy child, don't give in to sin"
It's driving me crazy
The urge to forsake thee
Yet, something shifts within this wicked bliss
I swore I'd never sin again
But my patience's running thin
Student council breathing down my neck
I wonder if they're hiding from me...?
Forbidden fruits before my eyes
And a taste that's so divine
My regrets rewriting history
I'm a sad, pathetic girl
Someone please tell me what to do...
Because, honestly, I just can't stop!
I've been trying so hard and I can't stop!
What would God think?!
And... I know I'm supposed to be a good girl, but...
Somehow, I just can't control myself!
Every time I see them...
...touching skin to skin...
...my mind goes...
Kyaa-ah!
Could Eve be our idol?
Could she lead us through the light?
We'd all be disciples of her lemon-driven bite
Can somebody save me?
The urge to forsake thee
Still, something shifts within this wicked bliss
The power resting in my hands
For my God has other plans
In salvation, I can live my life...
...as an ordinary girl
I can't resist it anymore
'Cause I smell slow-burn galore
All the trauma from a cobblestone
Could never beat the devil in me
An honest sinner 'til I die
What's the harm if I don't mind?
With the paddle that empowers me...
...I can live a sinful life!
チェックワンツー！
Check one-two!
チェックワンツー！ Yeah!
Check one-two! Yeah!
あーあもう無理！文化祭
Ah, I can't take it anymore! The school festival...
言葉にダンスに…キャパオーバーです
The speeches, the dancing... I'm at my capacity!
心配無用のおまじない
Here's a charm so you don't need to worry...
きっと報われるその努力
Surely all that effort will pay off!
『笑顔になれ』
"Smile!"
ドキドキしてる
My heart is pounding...
ありえないくらい本気だし
I'm taking this unreasonably seriously!
まほう・が・か・か・る
A spell is being cast...
今日限りヒーロータイム
Just for today, it's hero time!
何とぞね？
Won't you please?
Let's go!
baby kiss♡ 照れないで 気持ち伝えてよ！
Baby kiss, don't be shy, tell me how you feel!
好き？
Love me?
好き！
Love you!
好き？
Love me?
好き！
Love you!
相思相愛好き
Mutual love! I love you!
メイク崩れても 髪が乱れても
Even if my makeup wears off, even if my hair gets messy,
好き？
Love me?
好き！
Love you!
好き？
Love me?
好き！
Love you!
絶対忘れない青春の1ページ
An unforgettable page of our youth!
Hi!
あーあ超きもちー！文化祭
Ah, this feels amazing! The school festival!
隣で笑ってる君のおかげだ
It's all thanks to you smiling right beside me!
弱気な私変えてくれた
You changed my timid self...
絶対最強のパートナー
My absolute strongest partner!
マジで「ありがとう」
Seriously, thank you!
カ・ク・セ・イ・し・て・る ファンサの効力マシマシで
I'm awakening! Amping up the fan service effect!
まほう・つ・よ・ま・る
The magic grows stronger!
終わりかけヒーロータイム
Our hero time is almost over...
延長、ね？
Time extension, okay?
Let's go!
baby kiss♡ 隠さずに 気持ち伝えてよ！
Baby kiss, without hiding it, tell me how you feel!
好き？
Love me?
好き！
Love you!
好き？
Love me?
好き！
Love you!
相思相愛好き
Mutual love! I love you!
おやつ食べたいし 帰宅いいですか？
I wanna eat snacks and go home, can I?
（ダメ！） ダメ？ （ダメ！）
(No way!) No? (No way!)
ごめんうそうそ こちらこそ帰さない
Sorry, j/k, j/k! Likewise, I won't let you go home!
Hi!
TakaMori for five years!
Can you guys keep it going?
いくよー！
Here we go!
かりちゃんは超かわいい？
Is Calli-chan super cute?
（かりちゃんは超かわいい！）
Calli-chan is super cute!
きあちゃんは超かわいい？
Is Kia-chan super cute?
（きあちゃんは超かわいい！）
Kia-chan is super cute!
Big ups! Everybody!
Danke schön
Thank you so much!
Are you ready?
3, 2, 1, Go!
まほう解けちゃうね…
The spell is breaking...
最後に聞かせてよ
Let me hear it one last time!
好き？
Love me?
大きな声で「好き」
Say "I love you" out loud!
メイク崩れても 髪が乱れても
Even if my makeup wears off, even if my hair gets messy,
好き？
Love me?
好き！
Love you!
好き？
Love me?
好き！
Love you!
絶対忘れない青春の1ページ
An unforgettable page of our youth!
Hi!
な×7 Yeah!
Na na na na na na na, yeah!
ダンダンダンダンダンダン
Dan dan dan dan dan dan!
あきらめの悪いヤカラ あんたなんかじゃ束ねてもかなわない
Persistent as hell, even if you bunch up, you can't match us!
くわばら くわばら くわばら
Kuwabara, kuwabara, kuwabara!
目にも留まらん速さ さがらんおし通すわがまま
At a speed too fast for the eye to follow, pushing through our selfish desires without backing down!
そこどきな 邪魔だ 俺はもう一人のあなた
Out of the way, you're in the way! I'm another version of you!
さだちゃん かやちゃん
Sada-chan, Kaya-chan...
五鬼到着になんだが
Though the five demons have arrived,
四時四十四分回ったら よっしゃ
once it turns 4:44, alright!
四尺四寸四分様が鎌鳴っちばんばら
The four-foot-four-inch master is ringing their sickle loud.
ええ 呼ぶ声がしたんなら 文字通りお疲れ様やん
Yeah, if a voice was calling out, then literally, good job today.
ハイレタ ハイレタ ハイレタ ハイレタ ハイレタ
I got in, I got in, I got in, I got in, I got in.
必死で這い出た先で霧は晴れた
All of the fogginess lifted up as I escaped and writhed.
凹と凸がうまく噛み合ったら
Even when things attach, elements none would think would ever match,
痛みが重なったなら
even when hurt really overlaps,
心 体 頭 みなぎっていく
now our bodies, hearts, and minds have changed,
なんだか背中にいま羽が生えたならば
if we both have wings unfurl on our backs and ease the weight,
闇からおさらば ええ
I will say goodbye to all the pain, ay,
飛び立っていく彼方 ええ
from the darkness, we will fly away, ay.
心 体 頭 懐かしい温かさ
Now our bodies, hearts, and minds have changed with the warmth of those nostalgic days,
足元にいま花が咲いたならば
if the flowers start to bloom at our feet and still remain,
闇からおさらば ええ
I will say goodbye to all the pain, ay,
飛び立っていく彼方 おう
from the darkness, we will fly away, ay.
何度だって生きる お前や君の中
I'll keep living again and again within his or your head,
まぶたの裏や耳の中
right in those eyelids and ears till the end,
胸の奥にいついてるメロディー リズムに いいえ
right where the gut-wrenching melody beats, haunting deep, rhythmically.
今日も三途の川のど真ん中
Yeah, again in the middle of hell so hot,
積み上げてく top of top
pilin' up stones to the top of top,
鬼とチャンバラ the lyrical chainsaw massacre
slaying the demons per the lyrical chainsaw massacre.
渡る大海原 歌歌い singin' "sha-la-la"
Crossing the sea, openly singing alone with a "sha-la-la",
払いたいのだろう？ 祭り前までの札束
so you can be forgiven, bring more money for all ya flaws.
誰が開いたかパンドラ あとは何があっても知らんがな
Somebody opened up Pandora's box for fun, I don't care what is next for us.
数百年前待ったか 超久しぶりのシャバだ
It's been a few centuries, but I've only just waited to see enough.
ガキや若葉まだこっち来んじゃねえよ 馬鹿が
All of you kids as one, don't you come all this way yet, oh damn, you're dumb.
今確実に目が合ったな こういうことかをシャマラン
Well, I'm pretty sure that you looked so tough, so you showed us, Shyamalan.
ハイレタ ハイレタ ハイレタ ハイレタ ハイレタ
I got in, I got in, I got in, I got in, I got in.
眠りあきた先で君が待ってた
I got all tired of sleeping, yet you waited there all night.
縦と横が肩を抱き合ったら
Even when they embrace, elements clashing face to face,
怒りが消え去ったら
even when anger starts to fade,
心 体 頭 みなぎっていく
now our bodies, hearts, and minds have changed,
なんだか背中にいま羽が生えたならば
if we both have wings unfurl on our backs and ease the weight,
闇からおさらば ええ
I will say goodbye to all the pain, ay,
飛び立っていく彼方 ええ
from the darkness, we will fly away, ay.
心 体 頭 懐かしい温かさ
Now our bodies, hearts, and minds have changed with the warmth of those nostalgic days,
足元にいま花が咲いたならば
if the flowers start to bloom at our feet and still remain,
闇からおさらば ええ
I will say goodbye to all the pain, ay,
飛び立っていく彼方
from the darkness, we will fly away.
何度だって生きる
I'll keep living again and again
お前や君の中
within his or your head,
まぶたの裏や耳の中
right in those eyelids and ears till the end,
胸の奥にいついてるメロディー リズムに いいえ
right where the gut-wrenching melody beats, haunting deep, rhythmically.
Fortune Spinner
[Song: Fortune Spinner]
There's an answer out there somewhere
When the Muses whisper "truth or dare?"
The hands of fate play tug-of-war
But no one's keeping score
Stay the course and be tenacious
'Cause the future is a game of chance
The chips are down, but I'm all in
I play until I win!
I'm not gonna give up now
The wheels of fortune circle back around
A new turn in the betting ring
A maze of outcomes drawn in golden string
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
A wild chase
a frantic pace
I got to try my luck, I'm spinning fate
Ah... la da da da da da
I'm always spinning fate
Whoah yeah
Spin the roulette, see where it falls
Testing the limits and betting it all
Round and around, jumping into the circle
Over and over, a test of will
Oh, the game is never easy
And the outcome is a mystery
But these are fates worth betting on
Their threads unbroken
Called to life by flaxen string
Casting lots together at the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet
I spin back 'round with every chance I get
The wheel turns and the die is cast
The time has come for fate to change at last
And if it's black or red, I'm moving up ahead!
A perfect chance
a daring dance
I'll spin this thread of fate with my own hands
Ooh la la la
I'm taking fate into my hands
Whoah, yeah
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
New song, new song, new song!
やった！
We did it!
Yeah! It's our first song as a trio, you guys!
Yeah, trio!
Ah, true!
We moved over a little fast...
Now that I'm thinking about it...
Yeah! It's only like two minutes.
That's a good workout.
All the Zoomers like it short nowadays, huh?
That's what everybody says.
Not me. Definitely not.
Unfortunately, this was also the last song for this live!
Yeah, but the music video...
...for our 5th anniversary song, "Fortune Spinner", will premiere on the Hololive English Official YouTube channel...
...right after this concert! So make sure you stick around, okay?
Don't miss it!
Make sure you watch it a lot and loop it a lot!
So desu ne! So desu ne!
We still have some celebrating to do though, right?
That's right. I think it's time, because it's the end, that we kind of celebrate ourselves here. 5 years!
Are we ready for that?
Yes! We're ready, okay? Let's do it!
What is that cake over there that is not mine?
Big cake!
Big, big, big, big, big cake! Come on! Come on!
Let's talk about how delicious it looks!
Yeah, now I can see it!
It's big, too. It's almost bigger than Ina!
Oh yeah! Hey, stop, stop, stop! Not now, not now!
Don't take off the strawberries!
Hold your horses! Let's eat it later and celebrate!
And look, the trophies! Yeah!
We can do an award show, right? Staff somewhere...
Wait, did we actually get real trophies?
Yeah! They were listening! Thank you!
They followed our shopping list accordingly.
5 years, we deserve an award.
Yeah, we have so many meaningful accomplishments, so let me see what they all are, okay?
What's it gonna be? Should I start? I'll take mine.
Bless you! Sorry!
Ta-da-da-da!
I'm not trying to disrupt your award! What did you get? What did you get?
Hi, everybody! My award is...
I think it says... most cooked? Cooked the most?
She's cooking in HoloEN!
Let her cook! Let her cook! Let her keep doing it!
She has been cooking a lot. She has a lot of meals!
Thank you. I think that's what that's about. Mostly it's about, you know...
...me living a healthy lifestyle and cooking many meals at home, yeah.
I wish I could cook for you girls someday!
I hope you guys enjoyed my performances today!
I am so proud to stand here with my genmates...
...even on this day, after so many years.
I will continue to work hard, of course...
...so that I can maybe gather even more awards!
I will put this on my shelf at home...
...where my cats will also probably put a lot of fur on it, or knock it down!
Oh no! They like to do that!
Is it out of real glass? It's kind of heavy! Be careful.
Thank you guys so much! I love you girls!
It's been an honor so far...
...so let's do our best together!
Thank you for this award!
Who's the next one? Who's next?
Is it Ninomae Ina'nis?
Me? Oh, what's my award gonna be? Let's see.
Most violent?
Most violent? No, no, no! All right.
My award... is...
...Most Time Spent on the Floor Award!
Oh, that I believe! Yay!
Thank you! Thank you! I know you guys probably think I would never get this award...
...but you know, I worked so hard to stay on the floor.
Very unprecedented.
And yeah, not only did I stay on the floor, I, you know, really did my best to...
...practice dancing and singing this year to perform well with you guys!
And I hope that you guys see that as well! Thank you so much for all your support!
I'll continue to do my best with these girls!
Yeah! Myth! Let's keep doing it! Thank you Myth!
And last, but not least... me!
Oh, what could it be? Could it be our sneezer?
The serial sneezer!
Most sneezes in the Myth 5th Anniversary Showcase!
Well, actually, my trophy is for... ta-da!
Best Worst Luck Award! Especially in games where there are microtransactions!
Oh no! That's not so positive!
I mean, I've seen it happen in real life! Real time!
With the dedication, the determination to pull a signed card or not! I'm not gonna give up yet!
Real quick, I'm gonna be very sappy...
Yeah, okay, go ahead!
I really like that line, "I'm not..."
...give up yet, because... because...
I'd like to think that we're not gonna give up yet,
because there's still so much that I want to do,
the three of us together,
together, you know?
Um, and I didn't think that I would be here five years from the start with you guys.
Same.
Yeah, I really thought I'd be out of here.
Same!
Um, but now, I can't... I can't see a future where I'm not here with you guys, so for now...
Aww, that's so sweet!
Callie, shush. Okay.
So because of that, I'm not gonna give up yet. I don't want to give up yet. So let's do our best together.
Oh yeah, the wrapping music, the jingle is playing!
I'm just gonna start talking about nothing because that annoys me when they play the jingle to tell me to shut up.
Callie, you're a rapper! Rap! Rap!
This morning I ate a bagel and it had cream cheese on it and it was delicious, but it went over my...
Oh my god, you're so mean!
I had a big struggle with my trailer...
Okay, okay, it's fine.
Anyway, you can't get rid of me!
You can't get rid of...
...any of us, hopefully!
Well everybody, all good things come to an end, unfortunately,
but thank you so much to the hololive English community for supporting us continuously for 5 years.
Thank you to the girls today and all the staff-san that supported us also for the celebration who gave us the trophies.
Yeah, once again, congratulations to us!
Yay! To five years! To hololive English!
Thank you! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Peace!
Wait, we forgot the merch!
The merch!
Merch! Merch, please!
Merchandise!
Next up is the merchandise announcement!
We have hololive English -Myth- 5th Anniversary Celebration merch being released!
Let's look at the details. Check it out!
First up, we've got the Mirror Acrylic Panel.
It's designed so that the surroundings and background of the illustration have a metallic mirrored vibe.
So cool! I absolutely love this illustration. Hope you guys do too.
Next up, we have the Collection Cards!
These cards feature a shiny metallic finish, and you can choose from three different designs.
Also, the back side is matching for us all.
Make sure to get the one from your oshi for sure!
Next up, we have the Coin Medals!
Our shiny 5th anniversary commemorative coin medals, there's one design for each member.
And the back side also has a common design.
They come in an antique gold-plated finish inside the original packaging. Ooh, so shiny!
Oh man, everything looks so good, but I'm especially interested in what we have to show you guys next.
Next up, we have the Anniversary Hats!
So first up, Anniversary Hat - Mori Calliope!
This one uses a soft, fluffy fabric.
The Death Sensei part is removable, so you can also rock it without him.
Make sure that you check it out. It's super stylish! I love the shape so much, and...
...all of my members Dead Beats voted on it together, so hope that you guys will enjoy.
Next up, we have mine! The Anniversary Hat from Takanashi Kiara looks like this!
Decorative parts are removable. It can be worn reversibly, inside out,
so you'll have a different color then!
And it's a bucket hat style design which we didn't have before for me, very fashionable, I must say!
Last but not least, we have my hat, the Anniversary Hat - Ninomae Ina'nis!
The ribbon part is removable, and the patches are super cute, too!
You can wear it to become Takodachi. Yes!
And yeah, you can mix and match with or without the ribbon for different looks!
So everybody, be sure to check our merch out!
And that concludes our 5th Year Anniversary Stream!
hololive English -Myth-!
FORTUNE SPINNER